album. It rocks. How are you feeling at this moment, releasing such a, I think it's a personal
and creative body of work into the world. Honestly, I feel very, I feel excited because
I haven't done music in a really long time. And the reason I left music originally was because
it just wasn't any fun focusing more on the business than the music. People didn't really
care about the business. I mean, they didn't care about the music. They only cared about the
business. And so it feels really exciting to have found my way back to this medium and to be
receiving such a strong reception for the stuff that I sat here and made in this house. I just
really hunkered down and figured it out. And when I say figured it out, I don't just mean the tech
aspect. I mean, taking the information, the knowledge, the values that I espouse in a lot
of my like talking head content and putting that in a creative medium. Oh, brilliant. Cause I,
my next question naturally is what inspired this project? I think for what it's worth,
I've been moving towards now that I'm here, I feel like I've been moving towards this. I just didn't
know. Um, because the whole point of, you know, the whole point of my purpose of being here,
like in this time, in this realm is to change people's vibration. And I have gone through
different methods of doing that. And then landing here at music, you're like, well, music is naturally
like the most effective way to change folks' vibration. So like, what took you so long? And what
took me so long is that I needed to come into music with a clear focus. I needed to come into music
with an intention beyond just doing music. And I know for some people that's enough. Uh, for me though,
it needed to be more. And here we are. Also, I guess I just got tired of talking.
Um, but now you're singing emotional truth. Um, were you most, I suppose, determined to capture
in this project? I wanted to capture intentional elevation, action, decolonization. I wanted to
capture possibility, right? Because one of the things I hear from folks all the time is like,
so if we burn it down, then what I'm like, how is that even like possible that you can think that
that's like, this is it. That's, that's where we're at. This is it. So when I say truth translator,
I am saying there are truths out here that we need to translate into actions, right? Into,
into, um, movement. And that's why I also say it's not just, it's not a movement. It's movement music.